DirectorHomeless: Hey
toolegit2quit_: In a previous stream you said you were rich. Why do you enforce being a subscriber to watch precious streams ?
Rabidwh0re: Looking forward to this stream 👍
nic0latesla: hello geohot
toolegit2quit_: I guess that's a good reason ?
DirectorHomeless: you realise you can just watch them on youtube @toolegit2quit_
toolegit2quit_: Wait really ? @directorhomeless where ?
lancesan1ty: have you tried leela chess already?
any_available_username: catching you live PogChamp
DirectorHomeless: can't paste the link :/ just search geohotz slam though
alluxua: shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1 shamrock1
any_available_username: you really want to master chess huh
thisisweeezy: brooooooooooooo
35209: Neural Net to solve chess? We're going to need another Yerbe Matte.
thisisweeezy: cheer1
35209: lool
thisisweeezy: it's not cheating
any_available_username: if you keep thinking you will reach that point urself, so no its not cheating
DirectorHomeless: Even Newton stood on the shoulders of giants. Look it up.
35209: It's my belief that Neural Nets are not the optimal way to approach the 3600 grandmaster level.
quillford: grandmasters aren’t even close to 3600
quillford: the best human grandmasters are officially rated below 3000. top 10 or so are above 2750
35209: The best Chess engines are an order of magnitude better than any human, Deep blue is 3700 I think. The best human at any point in history was like 2800.
thisisweeezy: nice shirt
quillford: yeah but rating engines doesn’t really work
thisisweeezy: only a grand master?
35209: Hahvahd
thisisweeezy: print
35209: The reason Neural Nets don't work well on Chess is because the game is absolutly chaotic. Completely bankrupt explorations can turn out to be masterstrokes.
niculw: What hardware does eon run? Some of my friends made a CNN accelerator for their bachelor thesis, they could run darknet 4.5 times faster with an FPGA and a pi3 than an i7 4710hq could (according to their paper)
thisisweeezy: what's up with the extra 4..?
thisisweeezy: agree -- no doubt!
upsidedownlemon: apt-get install pip3
DirectorHomeless: sudo python3 east_install pip
35209: Python is kind of a shit language anywho.
thisisweeezy: python is great
thisisweeezy: now we talking
thisisweeezy: music of the day?
thisisweeezy: hahaa
thisisweeezy: it's impossible
any_available_username: lmao
35209: George this is your mother.
35209: STFU
thisisweeezy: "natural talent"
35209: If you want to improve your chess game, one way to do is it to just observe and analyze the games between supercomputers.
thisisweeezy: "A FEN string (e.g., rnbqkbnr/pppppppp/8/8/8/8/PPPPPPPP/RNBQKBNR w KQkq - 0 1) consists of the position part board_fen(), the turn, the castling part (castling_rights), the en passant square (ep_square), the halfmove_clock and the fullmove_number."
thisisweeezy: haha
thisisweeezy: nice
35209: Clowns I spot um and I can't stop laughing.
DirectorHomeless: Here come the copyright police
35209: Pasty white boys like the black alpha girls.
thisisweeezy: sick mussssic
quillford: https://youtu.be/6ygQMw4rBHg?t=656
KhaosVFX: GEOHOT
thisisweeezy: ha
35209: COPYRIGHT POLICE HANDS UP DON'T SHOOT.
DirectorHomeless: 35 years iirc is the expiry
thisisweeezy: https://gulfnews.com/news/asia/india/12-year-old-indian-one-of-youngest-grandmasters-1.2241333
35209: Google's AlphaZero is the best chess playing neural net in existence. There's an architecture whitepaper I read a year ago.
any_available_username: haHAA
35209: Alphazero dominated Stockfish, which is the next best algorithm.
gigafact: Hello George
thisisweeezy: lol
kuhrect: is he building his own chess AI?
thisisweeezy: 10 seconds
35209: I wrote code for a primitive for-loop chess engine like 15 years ago. For every possible move, look forward and pick the best one.
thisisweeezy: haah
any_available_username: lmao
gigafact: George can you do something for me? Go to https://www.twitch.tv/dashboard and add your stream to Programming game and community.
35209: Q-Learning Hierarchical Hidden Markov Models had good success with chess.
gigafact: Twitch has different categories for streaming and you streams fits perfectly to "Programming"
DirectorHomeless: that fan in the background is annoying
35209: TAKA TAKA TAKA TAKA TAKA
KhaosVFX: The fan was on
DirectorHomeless: it keeps coming on for 3 seconds
35209: A neural network we need to layout feature data and then specify target signal.
kuhrect: how old are you?
35209: The Fan is fine, they're trolling.
thisisweeezy: nice ipad
KhaosVFX: You should stream in 1080p
KhaosVFX: The fan is back on now
DirectorHomeless: THERE THERE THE FAN
thisisweeezy: better
3dvinci: Nice
any_available_username: stream under "Programming" category on twitch, i guess more people will come
gigafact: yes
KhaosVFX: now the fan is off
KhaosVFX: lol
DirectorHomeless: i give up
35209: Do you want neural net to evaluate board position?
any_available_username: im sure you did :)
kuhrect: lol stream pwnabletw :p
35209: I feel like I'm on an interview for a shitty crud app company.
35209: Define what are the feature data and what is the target prediction.
35209: Click here to download 243 petabyte chess.dat
thisisweeezy: MATE
quillford: use an incognito tab
35209: Chess is nothing like driving a car.
thisisweeezy: hah
thisisweeezy: you mean it's more complicated?
35209: Chess is discrete and totally visible. Driving a car is the exact opposite of driving a car in almost everyway.
35209: do I hear a female voice?
gigafact: for how long is the streaming been going on?
kuhrect: !uptime
thisisweeezy: 20 mins
gigafact: cool thanks
35209: more than 45 minutes, he's 10% into writing machine learning for chess.
DirectorHomeless: remind is liar? the bear is sticky with honey...
thisisweeezy: 3%
thisisweeezy: order mcdonalds!
35209: Mickey dee's. Ten piece nuggets.
3dvinci: Ayyy
3dvinci: The Obama of Bugattis
any_available_username: at what bitrate you streaming?
KhaosVFX: 2000 kbps at 720p
gigafact: George add your stream to programming community as well!
gigafact: https://www.twitch.tv/communities/programming
any_available_username: you saw that from "Show video stats" @KhaosVFX ?
thisisweeezy: chicken fried rice no chicken
35209: geohots is an enigma wrapped in a mystery, wrapped in a wheat burrito shell.
DirectorHomeless: can you bump the bitrate a bit? don't mind the 720p but bitrate feels low
thisisweeezy: lol
35209: Needs more Adenosine receptor inhibitors.
thisisweeezy: natural water!
KhaosVFX: this has too much carbon and chemicals LOL
KhaosVFX: ^ from periscope
35209: I tried one because of you, it has some snappiness to it.
gigafact: is your apple product too slow to stream on higher quality? so much for quality apple products haha
35209: Geohots is poor, can't afford a fast internet connect. Subscribe and donate.
thisisweeezy: lol
thisisweeezy: if not, lower it
quillford: cheer1
gigafact: someone subscribe for $24.99 Sub half goes to twitch anyway lol
rechka_rhine: yo
rechka_rhine: when's the new album
rechka_rhine: coming out
35209: I'm in process of sending you $10
rechka_rhine: dude I listened to your music so much
DirectorHomeless: any lower and we're at periscope levels of shittyness. that rav4 stream looked like lego
rechka_rhine: what book
thisisweeezy: 4k!
rechka_rhine: oh word
thisisweeezy: cheer1 cheer1
gigafact: all he needs for better periscope streams is streamlabs mobile app. periscope is really trash app
quillford: cheer1
35209: I have 1000 bits, I'm not sure what to do with it
thisisweeezy: haha
rechka_rhine: that vc money drying up bud?
any_available_username: Kappa
35209: How do I convert the bits to money?
DirectorHomeless: new task: write a neural net that can scale up a 2000kbps bitrate to 8000kbps in near realtime
thisisweeezy: so poorrrr -- here is 1 bit cheer1
nic0latesla: what is it the name?
nic0latesla: book???
thisisweeezy: another bit here cheer1
any_available_username: weeezy make it rain
thisisweeezy: im a VC to twitchchess
thisisweeezy: rain ~ cheer1
thisisweeezy: more rain?
thisisweeezy: cheer1
any_available_username: moar plZ
thisisweeezy: IT IS $
3dvinci: YM baby
DirectorHomeless: 1 bit = 10 dollars
35209: I bought $10 in bits, trying to figure out how to give you? Or is this just a perk unlock thing?
thisisweeezy: haha, not that much
gigafact: ^lie
any_available_username: 100 is like 0.1 right ?
DirectorHomeless: shhhh
thisisweeezy: type "cheer1"
thisisweeezy: "1" could be changed to any number
gigafact: it takes a while to process bits to cash for streamer
DirectorHomeless: 1 bit = $1
thisisweeezy: like "2", "3" etc
thisisweeezy: america!
Dsplits: Hate is bad!
any_available_username: they hate themselves too
any_available_username: twitch is freeland Kappa
Dsplits: You got more muscle on your right arm than your left arm.. I wonder why..
35209: cheer 10
thisisweeezy: together
3dvinci: lol
thisisweeezy: cheer 1k
any_available_username: trying to quit smoking and george is filling my insomnia with these streams thank god
gigafact: how to use twitch prime sub without giving them any cc info?
thisisweeezy: hah
thisisweeezy: southpark
35209: The cheers don't do anything
thisisweeezy: rice eating
DirectorHomeless: use 'cheer10'
thisisweeezy: on twitch
3dvinci: No spaces bruv
thisisweeezy: cheer-rice
rechka_rhine: there's a social eating category
thisisweeezy: cheerrice
35209: cheer1000
thisisweeezy: damn!
3dvinci: Rich
thisisweeezy: ^^^^^^^
thisisweeezy: 1000!
gigafact: that is something 35209!
DirectorHomeless: @tomcr00s3 you got your $10, lets see the 4000kbps
thisisweeezy: damn!
Dsplits: They are defining G
thisisweeezy: wowow
KhaosVFX: change it 1080p bro
thisisweeezy: Gangster!
thisisweeezy: hah
any_available_username: you need to restart stream i think
thisisweeezy: hahahah
3dvinci: lmaooo
35209: WE NEED MORE POWER. FIRE UP KOWALSKIS NUCLEAR REACTOR
redmx96: you need to restart
thisisweeezy: you're rich now
thisisweeezy: finally rich!
any_available_username: my bad
DirectorHomeless: lmao
gigafact: no need to restart
KhaosVFX: there is no visual difference smh
gigafact: refresh stream
any_available_username: how much for 1080p now cause there is no difference hahah
KhaosVFX: exactly
thisisweeezy: thank you 35209
thisisweeezy: thank you @35209
gigafact: bitrate helps where there is a lot of movement and a lot of different color
thisisweeezy: hahah
thisisweeezy: you ban
thisisweeezy: it's not the keyboard
gigafact: you can try to guess what kind of keyboard from the sound
gigafact: or write a neural net to guess by the sound of the keyboard
thisisweeezy: rice eating in 3 mins!
DirectorHomeless: it's a shit one
rechka_rhine: 100%
rechka_rhine: looking at keyless keyboard
rechka_rhine: but
35209: He's talked about his keyboard ad nausium in prior videos. So don't ask. It's aLeopold FC900R Black PD Double Shot ABS Mechanical Keyboard
any_available_username: Danger – Mix (Unofficial)
rechka_rhine: do you use dvorak programmer?
thisisweeezy: stream rice eating -- you'd get rich!
rechka_rhine: or are you a qwerty normie
35209: devorak is stupid,
rechka_rhine: no u
thisisweeezy: what's devorak
DirectorHomeless: ok, so thus far, we've listened to gwen stefani, ordered uber eats, and upped the bitrate. things are going well
35209: Devorak is a shuffling of the keys that's supposedly 1% more efficient? It's not.
rechka_rhine: it feels nicer
thisisweeezy: 1%?
thisisweeezy: it's worth it ha
rechka_rhine: vim keys still work
thisisweeezy: no emacs
rechka_rhine: spacemacs
DirectorHomeless: where's the love fr nano
thisisweeezy: emacs get ban
35209: We're in paralasis by analysis.
any_available_username: LMAO
gigafact: haha
any_available_username: monkaS am i banned monkaS test
thisisweeezy: emacs hurts hands
gigafact: how are you guys feeling about everything you say here it's going on youtube ? :P
thisisweeezy: feel great
35209: A vortex appears above your avatar, a thumb of smite materializes and smooshes you like a bug. Banned.
gigafact: Kappa
thisisweeezy: PokMaskedpika
thisisweeezy: hotz never washes his clothes
thisisweeezy: his clothes are there for days
thisisweeezy: ever since the twitchslam days
thisisweeezy: cheer1
35209: We're stuck on implementing the "value" function that supposedly a cost function for board fitness. But neural net isn't the best tool for the job. It's a pipe wrench on a nail.
thisisweeezy: ha
thisisweeezy: here comes the rice eating stream!
thisisweeezy: riceeeeeee
thisisweeezy: this steam is worth it
rechka_rhine: why is jake paul ironically appealing?
thisisweeezy: cheer1 here you go
35209: Winning positions can be up to 80 moves away.
thisisweeezy: of course
thisisweeezy: thank @35209
thisisweeezy: donating cheer1 so you could afford air condition
35209: 1 bit is like 0.1 cents lol.
thisisweeezy: print((
35209: Vim can make a background highlighter for print statements without parens.
thisisweeezy: ha it's the love
thisisweeezy: cheer1
thisisweeezy: that counts
thisisweeezy: noooice
gigafact: rice is amazing
thisisweeezy: what's the name of the restaurant ?
Dsplits: damn...
thisisweeezy: heard ".... Thai"
Dsplits: no freedom of expression..
35209: We need more donations so we can afford an air conditioner.
rechka_rhine: rice and butter. 10/10
gigafact: yes proper AC is quiet and very very cold
35209: 8000 BTU air conditioners can be quieter than $5 fans.
thisisweeezy: so many choicessss
thisisweeezy: hotz will spend the next hour buying a fan
gigafact: look how many decibels ?
35209: I have an air conditioner that's like 25 dB. That's practically nothing.
thisisweeezy: MATE
thisisweeezy: makes me hungry too
35209: You've overdosed already, you need to up to cocaine or barbituates.
35209: Caffine is a cousin of cocaine
thisisweeezy: hah
Dsplits: How do you feel about nootropics?
thisisweeezy: drug expert!
35209: Neuroscientist in the house.
thisisweeezy: meth
35209: lol, gonna have to delete this vid.....
gigafact: LSD?
35209: I knew a guy who did a lot of LSD, he went on to attempt suicide.
alluxua: Is geohot doing weeds or lsd?
gigafact: did you tried it?
thisisweeezy: legaaaalize it
35209: Drugs are bad mmmmkay?
thisisweeezy: weeeeeed
35209: nooooooooooo
alluxua: Doing weeds is kind of like digging a tiny hole in your brain, sugar does the same thing
35209: The best high is from cardio and lifting at the gym in the morning. Lift bros.
alluxua: Jogging is about the same
joejohnthbest: loud ass keyboard
Dsplits: Do you still do anything that's related to security?
gigafact: it's not that loud but mic is right there
thisisweeezy: security is a scam
thisisweeezy: hah
35209: What's the end goal of this TwitchChess?
Dsplits: no
35209: Why redesign the wheel with this chess stuff?
thisisweeezy: it's a easy task
any_available_username: it beat you already, you seem to given up Kappa
alluxua: Gosh, I missed that part geohot starts to smoke weeds. Did the video record it?
3dvinci: with GUI?
thisisweeezy: it's gonna come
thisisweeezy: weed smoking is after rice eating
gigafact: CLI only I hope
thisisweeezy: best css designer in the world
alluxua: Gosh, I got to watch that part
thisisweeezy: ".ain't my web design skills sick? "
Dsplits: lol
35209: Stop swearing on stream and eat your vegetables.
HettyPatel: hey
HettyPatel: what language do you recommend for a beginner?
TrustyCaribou: cheer1000
thisisweeezy: python
thisisweeezy: @TrustyCaribou ^^^^^^^ 1000 bits
35209: here comes the moneytrain... hey money money money dollah dollah.
alluxua: Javascript
thisisweeezy: another $10 dollar @tomcr00s3
thisisweeezy: bump the bits
thisisweeezy: hahaa
thisisweeezy: cheer1
TrustyCaribou: thanks for the great content
Dsplits: @HettyPatel Go with C
3dvinci: More bitrate den
upsidedownlemon: What are we doing here?
Dsplits: I'll give you money.. how much do you want?
35209: Neural net chess = learning.
alluxua: I gave you bits, but you never said thank you
thisisweeezy: weed smoking
upsidedownlemon: What kind of neural net?
thisisweeezy: rice eating
thisisweeezy: complicated neural nets
thisisweeezy: maybe geo can't explain -- i don't know what kind
thisisweeezy: * can
35209: @alluxua you do realize that geohots has more money in his bank account than all 45 of us in this channel will ever earn in our lifetimes, right? So your donation of 3 dollars didn't impress.
Bitcoin__: I've actually been thinking of making a chess game, but sadly I only write in VB.net :S
thisisweeezy: write it in assembly
thisisweeezy: lol
thisisweeezy: life is great!
Dsplits: @Bitcoin__ Only god's know that language!
alluxua: @35209 , I am so heart broken. Watched so many twitch ads to make that $3
Dsplits: @HettyPatel Best language to start with is machine code..
joker2k999: columns? row? your language is complex.
3dvinci: LUL
thisisweeezy: C
joker2k999: really? now your trolling.
thisisweeezy: 01010101010101001
joker2k999: 001101100011100
Dsplits: @joker2k999 Which instruction set are you using?
alluxua: shamrock1 shamrock1
joker2k999: lol, the noob one
35209: Real programmers don't write machine code, they use a prism and a steady hand.
Dsplits: @35209 Good one
joker2k999: what? no abacus?
35209: Emacs has Ctrl-Alt-left-butterfly- b
thisisweeezy: C instruction
joker2k999: theres a brew package out there for everyone...
35209: Bitshifting ooh yeah.
joker2k999: how about 1 or 0?
thisisweeezy: 1
Dsplits: Prolog is where the money is at
thisisweeezy: nand2tetris is a good course on coursera
3dvinci: LOL I feel you man
joker2k999: lol. the weed normally helps w/ that
thisisweeezy: ha
thisisweeezy: prolog is the shit
35209: Make geohots the biggets twitch streamer. Smash that notification button.
Dsplits: Can I recommend a song?
thisisweeezy: so is haskell
thisisweeezy: smmmmmmmashed
joker2k999: lol
35209: lol
joker2k999: savage
Dsplits: Damn
Andrewnagyy: What' up bro
35209: 20000 bits for a song. lol. Sounds like a bargain.
joker2k999: and smash that like button. didn't think there was a like button....
joker2k999: or 20000 bits in machine code...which is clearly an overflow....
desg92: wheres twitchslam
gigafact: ^
35209: What's a Tier 1 sub?
thisisweeezy: https://twitter.com/mattwhitlockPM/status/1010005280506220544
thisisweeezy: new subscriber! nice
joker2k999: so are we writing a chess py program just to stay sharp.... or....
Networks: there's different subscriber levels
gigafact: Tier 1 is $4.99 / Month
thisisweeezy: yes
Networks: tier 1, $5; tier 2, $10, etc
thisisweeezy: just for staying sharp
3dvinci: Dsplits put his money his mouth is
joker2k999: bet
alluxua: A month? Or just an one time fee?
thisisweeezy: only write useless stuff
Networks: a month
gigafact: for as long as you want
3dvinci: Donate me a sub
35209: I want to buy Comma-AI stock when it goes public.
gigafact: who said it will ever go public?
Dsplits: @35209 Visionary
alluxua: @35209 , when it is going public, it is too late to get in
35209: For 30000 bit donation, we can be even more obnoxious sluping up our tai fried rice.
35209: no, please explain
thisisweeezy: saw 0s and 1s
joker2k999: lol, says the guy w/ the yacht
Bitcoin__: Doesn't Comma.Ai pay good enough?
35209: I could float your yacht in my yacht's starbord pool.
Dsplits: lol
thisisweeezy: 40k/yr
joker2k999: change the world right...
Dsplits: Yes I did
35209: tear 1 sub
joker2k999: lol
Dsplits: @35209 ...
thisisweeezy: 41k
Networks: how many 0days do i have to find to get into harvard?
3dvinci: Buy love
joker2k999: so shallow, i love it
35209: George is a big advocate of college educations.
joker2k999: the woman bro
alluxua: @bitcoin__ , they got 3M investment about 2 years ago. And roughly they have 10-15 employees in the past 2 years. So do the maths. They got another 5M most recently
3dvinci: All feels the same
thisisweeezy: geo brutally loves MIT
EstevesxDbr: Why you type so slow ? Have you got some type of hand dysfunction ?
35209: lol
thisisweeezy: social prove
thisisweeezy: proof
3dvinci: All you need is the internet baby
joker2k999: speak on it bro
thisisweeezy: wan truth? subscribe to this channel !
rechka_rhine: nah truth is interacting with people
gigafact: preach
Networks: I hate my younger self for not holding onto more bitcoin lol
3dvinci: People are aight
3dvinci: Nice pass time sometimes
nic0latesla: Have you try hack facebook????
thisisweeezy: me too
thisisweeezy: hodl
Networks: lmao
Networks: I had 10 litecoins that I lost
35209: Donations to the channel increased the number of viewers.
Networks: and a decent amount of bitcoin lost due to gambling
thisisweeezy: bought 1.5 and sold it real quick back in 2015
joker2k999: just wait till he hits the bowl, then we'll really get some "truth"
3dvinci: Damn
Networks: i had around .5 in 2014
desg92: the bowl?
Dsplits: Got 15 bitcoins atm
Networks: when it was worth like $250
thisisweeezy: 0.5
gigafact: Best video about Bitcoin https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KV5QlSgq7lg
thisisweeezy: 15 damnnn
thisisweeezy: how to turn 100k into 10k -- nowadays
Networks: BTC is about to dip under 6k
thisisweeezy: so rich
Andrewnagyy: BTC is going away man, it was a ponzi scheme
35209: 15 bitcoins is what? like $15000 USD?
thisisweeezy: haaaa
Dsplits: Good one
thisisweeezy: EOS
joker2k999: lol. good one
3dvinci: Elastos baby
thisisweeezy: < US dollar
35209: I don't know what EOS is
thisisweeezy: shitcoins
3dvinci: Put it in Elastos
3dvinci: lmaoo
alluxua: EOS is a scam.
35209: I invest my retirement in Hatian Penny stocks.
Dsplits: soo many magic numbers
Bitcoin__: The biggest mistake I made was gambling 2.7 BTC at 360$ and selling 250 LTC at 4,05$
rechka_rhine: a coin's potential value is a function of how many dumb rich people it can attract, and EOS is clearlfy doing very well in that front
EstevesxDbr: Theter is a great way to hedge crypto exposure without coverting into fiat
thisisweeezy: ranked 1
thisisweeezy: EOS
rechka_rhine: scam
thisisweeezy: RIPPLE scam!
thisisweeezy: BTC semi-scam
rechka_rhine: sorta scam
rechka_rhine: tron is a scam
thisisweeezy: TRON is HUUUUGE scam
rechka_rhine: bittorrent is an irrelevant company
alluxua: I hedge bitcoin, ETH with consumer stocks and tech stocks, so far so good
Dsplits: how is tron a scam?
rechka_rhine: grincoin is kinda cool
rechka_rhine: http://grin-tech.org/
rechka_rhine: but you can't just give out addresses
rechka_rhine: I think you have to negotiate every transaction
thisisweeezy: goto 10
rechka_rhine: but nodes can prune most of the block chain
35209: Rewrite your production code in Pony and Jerlang.
35209: It has goto.
thisisweeezy: 1: TRON is scam
thisisweeezy: goto1
rechka_rhine: devs seem like nice people
rechka_rhine: but all cryptos are scam
Dsplits: Crypto-Currencies are all scams.. What matters is the concept of the blockchain
gigafact: this stream is amazing we need to at least once a week
thisisweeezy: hmmmmm
thisisweeezy: really bruvh, blockchain
thisisweeezy: blockchain is over-rated
Dsplits: The future of the blockchain is smart contracts
rechka_rhine: everything is over rated
35209: IBM is trying to subsume a blockchain to try to make it paletable for the government. Embrace extend extinguish.
thisisweeezy: maybe
rechka_rhine: we're all gonna die
thisisweeezy: yes we're
thisisweeezy: so let's enjoy it!
rechka_rhine: never seen someone use "we're" like that
alluxua: Blockchain will settle down of its tech position very soon, as the AI. It happened to big data 3 years ago
rechka_rhine: shill me elastos
35209: Are you shilling for your drinks? Are you doing this for the money? lol
Networks: using we're like that is the reason god abandoned us
rechka_rhine: 27 github stars
Dsplits: @alluxua No.. is too early for that
rechka_rhine: to the moon
35209: lol
thisisweeezy: everyone starts it
35209: I get the raspberry tea. it's better
thisisweeezy: instaban
rechka_rhine: have you heard of urbit george? not a crypto
rechka_rhine: oh no
Dsplits: That's right
desg92: lmao
rechka_rhine: I guess it has an asset
gigafact: lol
thisisweeezy: $$
rechka_rhine: urbit.org
thisisweeezy: Bruhchain yo
35209: Safe AND reliable!
Dsplits: Lol same shit that tron is doing...
joker2k999: oh wow. i had to stop my work to enjoy this
Crabtr: LUL
thisisweeezy: tol you about TRON
alluxua: Have a look of their github pull request
any_available_username: @joker2k999 same lol
thisisweeezy: smash that SUBSCRIBE button!
35209: Sarcasm level is over nine thousand.
rechka_rhine: fuck I feel myself getting retarded trying to read these whitepapers
redmx96: calm down Richard Hendricks
35209: The caffine is irritating your neurons.
thisisweeezy: whitepapers
rechka_rhine: that's the idea
thisisweeezy: lol
Networks: LOL
rechka_rhine: 27 github stars bro
35209: Cellphone environment...
thisisweeezy: HUUUUUUUGE scam
rechka_rhine: george
rechka_rhine: urbit.org
rechka_rhine: elastos
thisisweeezy: wait
35209: hold on.
thisisweeezy: i'll give one
rechka_rhine: thoughts?
Networks: ill give u a star <3
rechka_rhine: is it a cult?
rechka_rhine: am I in a cult?
joker2k999: bro, i will tune in to watch you shit on cryto or (insert any IT related thing)any day of the week.
rechka_rhine: it's super cool
wiiziwiig: just me or did stream stop?
35209: I starred your shitty Chess app bro.
rechka_rhine: it's basically still just a chat app now
alluxua: Who are in their team? Overall it is a tech start up
gigafact: they used latex to write it at least
joker2k999: oh gawd, is he doing research, why are you reading white paper
Rabidwh0re: Yo, when will you stream twitchico?
thisisweeezy: 6 stars!
thisisweeezy: mindf*ck
alluxua: White paper rarely means nothing. The implementation means a lot
joker2k999: lol @batman. thats funnyAF.
thisisweeezy: it means a lot to geo lol
thisisweeezy: please give geo more self-esteem
35209: PLEASE UPVOTE: https://github.com/geohot/twitchchess
alluxua: Star chess?
rechka_rhine: aaron
joker2k999: your dirs are always some comical ish
rechka_rhine: let's be friends
rechka_rhine: we live in the same city
rechka_rhine: aaron mill, I see you
joker2k999: should..,
Dsplits: You just killed that mans dreams
thisisweeezy: followed all the star-ers
thisisweeezy: let's get 10!
thisisweeezy: leet's validate Geo
miteydrill: preach it
Onedaymylove: is he being sarcastic can't tell
miteydrill: Father I crave seratonin
antranilandimetylu: What are you doing?
35209: Neural nets chess = learning
wiiziwiig: stars matter
thisisweeezy: maybe weed smoking tooo
antranilandimetylu: How is he leasing it?
antranilandimetylu: Learning
rechka_rhine: csv is the 2nd best file after .txt
Dsplits: @35209 You should be a mod
joker2k999: damn spaces...
thisisweeezy: magic
35209: Elevate me to mod, I will be firm but fair.
rechka_rhine: aaron, was it something I said?
joker2k999: i think csv was big in the 80s?
antranilandimetylu: It’s the simplest and best
thisisweeezy: he learns from stackoverflow and google
joker2k999: i don't think he learns, i think he just know
antranilandimetylu: But I meant
thisisweeezy: yeaaah
antranilandimetylu: How is he learning his ai
thisisweeezy: he knows lol
3dvinci: Been doin it
thisisweeezy: AI is scam
antranilandimetylu: Lmao
rechka_rhine: AI winter when?
rechka_rhine: AI winter 2.0*
thisisweeezy: https://twitter.com/drewconway/status/1010137695664951297
35209: Skynet won't be possible for at least 35 years. Beep Boop, No need to worry fellow humans.
thisisweeezy: it's call "statistics"
alluxua: If I say this chess python is quite boring, would I get kick out there or geohot would code something more interesting?
wiiziwiig: what is the original song to this beat?
wiiziwiig: sounds familiar
3dvinci: Would probly just ignore you
Dsplits: Sunny Day Real Estate - In Circles is a good song
rechka_rhine: thoughts on vaporwave?
thisisweeezy: what's vaporwave?
rechka_rhine: https://dreamcatalogue.bandcamp.com/album/--18
wiiziwiig: whats there to think about? are you saying something is vapor ware?
thisisweeezy: pretty nice music
rechka_rhine: https://beerontherug.bandcamp.com/album/floral-shoppe
rechka_rhine: just asking for opinions/recommendations
wiiziwiig: this guys is in the zone
rechka_rhine: true
wiiziwiig: i want to be in the zone like this guy
thisisweeezy: pytoooooorch
thisisweeezy: you'd need some weeed
Dsplits: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=41YqzHoCgk4
thisisweeezy: to be in this type of zone
joker2k999: bro we know you got that carter V man
wiiziwiig: oo vaporware is a band?
gigafact: this sounds nice
rechka_rhine: it's a genre
wiiziwiig: i thought you meant vaporware vaporware
alluxua: @tomcr00s3 , how about code deep learning on investment as you love money next time?
ABuffSeagull: @rechka_rhine good taste with that 2814 album, love that album
joker2k999: No binaural beats?
rechka_rhine: my favorite vaporwave album is https://telepathtelepath.bandcamp.com/album/--12
thisisweeezy: all japanese?
rechka_rhine: no
Onedaymylove: you watch this guy code, and you think when will the day come when I can code the things in my head onto the screen
thisisweeezy: is it originated from JP or something
rechka_rhine: nope
ABuffSeagull: most vaporwave is instrumental
wiiziwiig: this sounds like 5 songs mixed together
3dvinci: Binaural is trippy
thisisweeezy: @Onedaymylove one day
rechka_rhine: the first song isn't great
Onedaymylove: ohhhh nice one
thisisweeezy: hah
ABuffSeagull: most vaporwave uses japanese characters cause japanese is ＡＥＳＴＨＥＴＩＣ
rechka_rhine: telepath might actually be japanese idk
thisisweeezy: so A ESTHETIC
gigafact: everyone in the chat follow George to get notifications when he starts streaming. close to 1k followers on twitch!
thisisweeezy: CTRL C, V makes life miserable
redmx96: tensorflow?
3dvinci: Pytorch vs. Tensorflow?
thisisweeezy: 1k!
rechka_rhine: george
rechka_rhine: skip to song 2
rechka_rhine: on that album
rechka_rhine: on the blue one
thisisweeezy: geo is gonn be rich and he needs the validation from us LMAO
35209: Roll your own neural net... in Assembly.
wiiziwiig: was i the 1k follower?
thisisweeezy: daaaamn -- 1k
gigafact: I said close we are not there need more followers
thisisweeezy: here is one bit for being the the 1k th follower cheer1
Dsplits: @35209 You couldn't be closer to the truth
wiiziwiig: oo ok
gigafact: when is twitch going to feature George stream he is making twitchslam twitchchess this has to count for something right?
thisisweeezy: he is switching careers
thisisweeezy: soon
rechka_rhine: george should code an open source twitch
rechka_rhine: call it twitchtwitch
thisisweeezy: ohhh yeah
thisisweeezy: ^^^^ thumbsup
wiiziwiig: call it nottwitch
thisisweeezy: twitchtwitch
Dsplits: Geo when are you going to become a full time streamer?
thisisweeezy: and livesteam and twitchtwitch
rechka_rhine: next song
rechka_rhine: on that album
rechka_rhine: song 2
3dvinci: From vaporware to vaporwave
wiiziwiig: why is he reassigning x so many times?
thisisweeezy: idk
madebyollin: not a pytorch expert but seems likely that the nn.Module superclass is assuming you have all of the layers as properties for the other passes
thisisweeezy: ¯_(ツ)_/¯
rechka_rhine: don't you love having to sing in to a website to install cuda?
rechka_rhine: sign*
madebyollin: does cuda require signin or just cudnn?
rechka_rhine: or cudnn
thisisweeezy: smash that star button here: github.com/geohot/twitchchess/
rechka_rhine: the fact that nvidia forces you to open a browser to use hardware you bought from them
madebyollin: optimizer = optim.Adam([var1, var2], lr = 0.0001) ?
madebyollin: nvm
agentvenom2: what does this dataset contain? chess position -> probability of win?
thisisweeezy: think so
alluxua: how large of your training datasets?
thisisweeezy: huuuuge dataset
rechka_rhine: yea, coding neural nets feels so weird
rechka_rhine: writing code to write code
gigafact: inception?
rechka_rhine: no I just mean it feels clunky
alluxua: if you are just beginning ,try keras
rechka_rhine: it's still weird
madebyollin: is your net downsampling anywhere?
thisisweeezy: ML is hard
alluxua: Do you know how to tune those parameters?
rechka_rhine: von neuman machines are the wrong abstraction
Dsplits: free martin shkreli
rechka_rhine: tru
rechka_rhine: forgot about that guy
thisisweeezy: this stuff seems hard
madebyollin: https://discuss.pytorch.org/t/expected-stride-to-be-a-single-integer-value-or-a-list/17612 ?
madebyollin: * (other, e.g., the game is ongoing).
Dsplits: that chair seems uncomfortable
gigafact: He needs https://www.dxracer.com/ to be a proper streamer
joker2k999: lol
joker2k999: same chair different color
thisisweeezy: $$$$$$$$$$$
thisisweeezy: here we go again
thisisweeezy: another hour spent on amazon.com
joker2k999: its... good for office gaming
thisisweeezy: you get a chair
Dsplits: yes
dorkmo: fnatic is just a game clan
EstevesxDbr: yep
joker2k999: its amazon, you can get it tomarrow
gigafact: yep
Dsplits: 2 day delivery
rechka_rhine: no
rechka_rhine: get pewdiepie's chair
thisisweeezy: seems expensive
dorkmo: get a herman miller
thisisweeezy: a chair for $300 ?
Networks: fnatic is a CS:GO team? why buy a CS:GO team branded chair? lmao
rechka_rhine: lol
thisisweeezy: that's some expensive sh$t
decaprime: craigslist aeron
Dsplits: Yeah it's a good chair
joker2k999: yea, its the streamer chair bro
thisisweeezy: 5 star reviews on THEIR website!
joker2k999: ....wow. he has his own chair?
dorkmo: https://www.amazon.com/DOH-FD01-NR-Ergonomic-Executive/dp/B0711QC6Q9/ref=lp_7585024011_1_1?srs=7585024011&ie=UTF8&qid=1529898179&sr=8-1 amazon link
Dsplits: They are both the same
rechka_rhine: that's the chair I have
rechka_rhine: it's pretty nice
joker2k999: oh. yea... same thing, just sponsored
rechka_rhine: that's literally my chair
rechka_rhine: haha
dorkmo: twitchchair
thisisweeezy: next two steam: twitchtwitch, twitchchair
yyube_: How’s the company doing?
joker2k999: #goals. #focus
rechka_rhine: herman miller?
rechka_rhine: they're doing great probably
thisisweeezy: company is doing great but geo is switching career to be a full-time steamer
rechka_rhine: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aeron_chair
yyube_: thisisweezy??
yyube_: Lol
thisisweeezy: it's real
thisisweeezy: and geo needs stars on this repo: github.com/geohot/twitchchess/
yyube_: You’re definitely bullshitting
thisisweeezy: we can do it, let's get 10 stars
thisisweeezy: ask geo
madebyollin: you want 1, right?
alluxua: The greatest of geohot is he is totally transparent, even not hiding he is learning the basics of deep learning
madebyollin: since it's amount on each side?
rechka_rhine: no, yyube_, you don't understand. He's t h i r s t y for those stars.
yyube_: I know geo from the jailbreak scene
thisisweeezy: he's changed
yyube_: And for his company comma ai
rechka_rhine: he's born again
gigafact: AD for dx chair https://vimeo.com/198933442 so powerful lol
thisisweeezy: he's twitching fulltime
yyube_: Python?
rechka_rhine: yes
thisisweeezy: python and C
yyube_: Do any of you program?
yyube_: And what is he making rn?
Dsplits: use dim-X
alluxua: I do, Python on machine learning
madebyollin: he's making a neural net to predict chess outcomes, I think?
rechka_rhine: you have to be a programmer to be in this stream
yyube_: @rechka_rhine I only know python basics lol
gigafact: or you just watch George beautiful face...
rechka_rhine: get out ree
thisisweeezy: I choose latter
yyube_: I’m learning Java for school but I hate it
rechka_rhine: ew
rechka_rhine: gross
rechka_rhine: learn Idris
yyube_: Java sucks ass
alluxua: Is he offline?
thisisweeezy: argh, JAVA
yyube_: But I’m learning it for the AP test
rechka_rhine: he's in the zone
rechka_rhine: highschool??
yyube_: Because for some reason Java is the language for AP comp sick
alluxua: Weeds zone?
yyube_: Sci
yyube_: Yes
rechka_rhine: are you gonna be a programmer?
yyube_: Idk yet
thisisweeezy: every once a while, geo get out of zone and browse amazon.com
yyube_: I’m going into junior year
thisisweeezy: brogrammer
rechka_rhine: Java is the language because those people don't shoot where the world is going but where it is
alluxua: Seriously, is he on weed again?
yyube_: Why isn’t geo using Linux?
joker2k999: no, not yet
gigafact: multiplatform is the only good thing about java
alluxua: He has Ubuntu
rechka_rhine: because macos on the laptop, linux on the server
rechka_rhine: that's how you do it
yyube_: Gotcha
Dsplits: Don't rely on one technology.. Most of java jobs have been outsourced
rechka_rhine: you don't wanna fuck around with linux drivers and bs
yyube_: @rechka_rhine what’s the best resource to expand knowledge on python?
rechka_rhine: hmm
yyube_: @rechka_rhine I took a starter course that only taught up to functions.
alluxua: Courses Andrew ng deep learning
rechka_rhine: no he needs python not DL
alluxua: If you finish, you can kick geohot ass.
rechka_rhine: I recommend learn python the hard way book
gigafact: https://docs.python.org/ lol
dorkmo: party1
alluxua: Geohot needs to take that course as well
yyube_: Are books a better resource than online
Dsplits: Look up the book "Learning Python, 5th Edition "
rechka_rhine: I guess it's not free anymore
thisisweeezy: party1
rechka_rhine: https://learnpythonthehardway.org/python3/
thisisweeezy: for ME
rechka_rhine: the python 2 one is free
thisisweeezy: party1
rechka_rhine: https://learnpythonthehardway.org/book/
Dsplits: @gigafact You're right
rechka_rhine: I think books are better than courses yes
yyube_: But I should learn python 3, right?
rechka_rhine: but the main thing is you just have to make stuff
rechka_rhine: they are very similar
yyube_: I’m taking a Udemy java course, but it holds your hand too much and it’s easy af.
rechka_rhine: but yea python3 is the one you should be using
Dsplits: @yyube_ Before you start learning it.. think of why you want to learn python
thisisweeezy: liked how the chat is totally unrelated to the stream lol
yyube_: I would like to create automated software
alluxua: He went offline
gigafact: powershell
rechka_rhine: python is the best first language to learn, idk where you're going dsplits
Dsplits: You can do it from almost any language
Dsplits: @rechka_rhine I don't think it is
thisisweeezy: CUDA
ido1m: @rechka_rhine it really isn't lol
Th3R3dQu33n: so this guy used to jailbreak iOS operating systems?
Dsplits: is too abstract
rechka_rhine: it's a stupid debate, just learn python
yyube_: Python seems to be very simplistic in syntax compared to Java which seems wordy, correct?
thisisweeezy: GPU
ido1m: @rechka_rhine nice troll
rechka_rhine: yes
gigafact: @Th3R3dQu33n yes
yyube_: Where should I go after functions in Python?
thisisweeezy: GPUUUUUUGE
Th3R3dQu33n: @gigafact sweet!
Th3R3dQu33n: thx
gigafact: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Hotz
rechka_rhine: reading/writing files
joker2k999: ..of course you do..
gigafact: he really needs to update that wiki pic lol
alluxua: If you love money, 3 weeks basic Python, then 3 months coursera deep learning, and then 2 months fast.ai free training, if you are serious, you can be top
Th3R3dQu33n: @gigafact always thought Musk should have hired him
joker2k999: only took you all of 5 seconds
madebyollin: classes, list comprehensions, file reading/writing, how to use pip and install/use libraries
Dsplits: @yyube_ Do you even know what a byte is? How data structures are allocated in memory?
rechka_rhine: he's in highschool
yyube_: @D
yyube_: @dsplits yes
yyube_: Already learned that
yyube_: @dsplits that was the beginning of the java course
gigafact: it's better he did not join Tesla now we have https//comma.ai and it's amazing
joker2k999: waffles sound good right now
rechka_rhine: musk did try to hire him
thisisweeezy: this is deep -> "If you love money, 3 weeks basic Python, then 3 months coursera deep learning, and then 2 months fast.ai free training, if you are serious, you can be top"
gigafact: https://comma.ai
Dsplits: binary search tree? Stack? black tree? AVL-tree?
rechka_rhine: lots of cars come with lane assist now
thisisweeezy: it's going DOWN
joker2k999: lol
Dsplits: @yyube_ I'm not talking about the simple data structures.. there's more to it
thisisweeezy: !LOSS
Dsplits: Also take a course on linear algebra
rechka_rhine: || || | |_
yyube_: @dsplits where should I go to expand knowledge and do something productive over the summer?
yyube_: @dsplits I’m motivated to learn
rechka_rhine: reading writing files
rechka_rhine: then make something
ido1m: @yyube_ read books & create stuff
rechka_rhine: make a program that does something for you
yyube_: Ideas?
rechka_rhine: that's the part I've always struggled with
yyube_: Also, what books are the best books you recommend?
rechka_rhine: I already told you
ido1m: Best books for ... ?
rechka_rhine: be careful making lists of books to read as a form of procrastination :P
Dsplits: @yyube_ If I were you I would familiarize my self with basic computer science concepts.. then after that you can start learning about automation
rechka_rhine: I do that
thisisweeezy: we can do it 64%
rechka_rhine: https://learnpythonthehardway.org/book/
michiamozen: use udemy
michiamozen: for basics
yyube_: Ok, I’ll learn the basics on udemy
dorkmo: someone order a pizza
rechka_rhine: make a chat app on the command line
yyube_: That’s what I’m doing rn
gigafact: http://s-f-walker.org.uk/pubsebooks/pdfs/Julian_Jaynes_The_Origin_of_Consciousness.pdf
yyube_: But after I finish a udemy course, then what?
rechka_rhine: "okay it doesn't learn" fucking story of my life with DL
michiamozen: then you'll know the basics @yyube_
Dsplits: @yyube_ Look for "Introduction to Algorithms, 3rd Edition" or http://www.kitabxana.net/files/books/file/1354098277.pdf
rechka_rhine: make a program
rechka_rhine: knowledge isn't power. the application of knowledge is power
michiamozen: :haha:
Dsplits: @rechka_rhine You need to know how to mix theory and practice
yyube_: Thank you all so much
yyube_: One more question, how often is math actually used in programming and what type of math is used?
rechka_rhine: not often
Dsplits: depends
Dsplits: machine learning a lot of linear algebra
rechka_rhine: for 90% of programming jobs you basically never use any math
Dsplits: and some calculus
rechka_rhine: not even
Dsplits: @rechka_rhine yeah the shitty jobs
ido1m: @Dsplits Not at all lol
yyube_: I’m doing pre calc this upcoming school year
Dsplits: if you want to be a webdeveloper for the rest of your life dont learn math
rechka_rhine: if you're just using ML you don't even need to know it. if you're writting the libraries sure.
yyube_: And then calc BC senior year
dorkmo: party100
rechka_rhine: if you're making websites, you'll never use math
thisisweeezy: quaier mier
rechka_rhine: listen to george
dorkmo: listen
thisisweeezy: LISTEN UP
rechka_rhine: that's most conspiracy theorists
yyube_: Lol
rechka_rhine: geopolitics
thisisweeezy: earth is ROUND
Networks: LMAO
alluxua: @tomcr00s3 , geohot, take the deep learning class from Andrew ng on coursera seriously. For average people, it takes 3 months to finish. But for you, only 6 weeks. You will benefit a lot from it
rechka_rhine: no I meant the feeling of being in on a secret
thisisweeezy: earth is FLAT
thisisweeezy: lol
Sgtkill: So the earth is flat or did i not understand that correctly??
Dsplits: Knowledge
rechka_rhine: :underlined 100 emoji:
thisisweeezy: ohhhh man
yyube_: Is he writing code in the Mac terminal?
michiamozen: our body is STRAIGHT not ROUND, so the earth is FLAT
rechka_rhine: yes
thisisweeezy: party1
rechka_rhine: programmers use the terminal extensively
thisisweeezy: good good study, day day up
ido1m: @yyube_ it's called vim
rechka_rhine: it doesn't look like it, but it's the most powerful way to use a computer once you learn how
yyube_: I’m such a noob, but how did he get lines and stuff in the Mac terminal
Sgtkill: @michiamozen depends how much cake you eat Kappa
Dsplits: vim is a command line editor
thisisweeezy: 79 viewers!
rechka_rhine: https://www.digitalocean.com/community/tutorials/an-introduction-to-the-linux-terminal
hartator1: waho new record 81
michiamozen: linux terminal is all about ls, cd, and chmod
rechka_rhine: he's using https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vim_(text_editor)
gigafact: when we get to 100 George will rap
gigafact: he promised
thisisweeezy: oh yeaehhh
rechka_rhine: I'm telling my friends
Networks: mines all about rm
hartator1: hell yeah get him to 100
yyube_: Are most of you in or out of college?
thisisweeezy: 0 to 100 real quick
rechka_rhine: out
Networks: I'm a senior in HS
rechka_rhine: I need a jerb
yyube_: Did you major in cs?
rechka_rhine: I dropped out
rechka_rhine: but ye
hartator1: try "rm -rf / " in your Terminal app, best way to learn how to code.
yyube_: Y’d u drop out?
thisisweeezy: wut
rechka_rhine: tbh
rechka_rhine: I am not sure
Dsplits: I graduated last fall
rechka_rhine: but I did a semester and it was no cs
rechka_rhine: just introduction to java
rechka_rhine: and I thought this is retarded I'm out
rechka_rhine: went to work
Networks: the only formal programming class i've taken was on javascript lol
Sgtkill: Can you explain what you're doing for new viewers?
rechka_rhine: I went to make friends and I didn't make any
thisisweeezy: yyyyyyyyyyeah, so valuable
rechka_rhine: so /shrug
Networks: im pretty psyched
michiamozen: social_life = False
Dsplits: social_life = scam
yyube_: So first things first I should learn basics
Networks: life isn't existent to begin with
thisisweeezy: NET
yyube_: With books such as the python book @rechka_rhine recommended
any_available_username: LMAO
yyube_: The connect four meme lol
rechka_rhine: then make a program, then learn more theory like @Dsplits said
hartator1: if social_life == nil print "redditor"
rechka_rhine: reddit is gross
yyube_: Ok, no more questions. Thank you so much @rechka_rhine , @dsplits , and anybody else who gave me advice.
Dsplits: @yyube_ Yeah make sure that you actually apply the theory
rechka_rhine: do you have a github
michiamozen: if programmer == "beginner": programmer.use("notepad ")
rechka_rhine: @yyube_
gigafact: the speed of programming here is insane
gigafact: is anyone of you even close to this real life?
yyube_: @rechka_rhine yes, but no projects
thisisweeezy: who uses notepad
thisisweeezy: use paper
rechka_rhine: what is it
rechka_rhine: I'll follow you
thisisweeezy: search for meaning of life
Dsplits: @yyube_ true. @rechka_rhine made a valid point. Look at github repositories and learn from them
yyube_: yyube
rechka_rhine: reading other people's code is nice too
yyube_: Same as twitch
gigafact: yep everything is online if you look hard enough
dorkmo: cant get this content on cable
thisisweeezy: rename state ?
michiamozen: reading other people's code as an audiobook on audible is better
thisisweeezy: change 'state' to like '_state'
rechka_rhine: https://github.com/requests/requests/tree/master/requests is some nice code
thisisweeezy: cooooool brrrrrruh
yyube_: @rechka_rhine are you boris?
rechka_rhine: ye
yyube_: K
thisisweeezy: model.uncuda
Dsplits: Geo what time is bed time?
rechka_rhine: I also don't have projects, so we got that in common lol
ivanfremn: is this vim
ivanfremn: I code on Microsoft Word
rechka_rhine: yes
ivanfremn: Kappa
rechka_rhine: andrew ng did that
rechka_rhine: made me feel weird
thisisweeezy: i code in excel spreadsheet
rechka_rhine: writting matlab in Word
gigafact: atom is nice too
Dsplits: @ivanfremn Best editor ever
yyube_: Why not write code in IDE?
Dsplits: @thisisweeezy Even btter
alluxua: Use anaconda has everything
rechka_rhine: spacemacs is nice if you want to invest the time to learn both emacs, vim and the spacemacs keybindings
yyube_: Such as pycharm?
rechka_rhine: use an IDE
rechka_rhine: it's the fastest way to get started
thisisweeezy: bird
yyube_: And then learn vim and terminal later?
thisisweeezy: bill$on dollar company yo
Dsplits: is all personal preference. I like terminal because I can easily navigate through the system
rechka_rhine: learn terminal right away
ivanfremn: I code on a typewriter and then I scan the paper and use a program to transform the image into text
hartator1: true coder do `cat >> python` not text editors
dorkmo: billion dollar shave club
rechka_rhine: but vim isn't really necessary
yyube_: @rechka_rhine any recommended resource for that?
rechka_rhine: https://www.digitalocean.com/community/tutorials/an-introduction-to-the-linux-terminal
Dsplits: @ivanfremn That's the most productive way to program
rechka_rhine: or
Dsplits: vim is good.. I love emacs tho
ivanfremn: bruv your windows are overlaping
ivanfremn: how can you live like this
rechka_rhine: http://blog.teamtreehouse.com/introduction-to-the-mac-os-x-command-line
Dsplits: @ivanfremn ocd much?
rechka_rhine: if you're on macos
thisisweeezy: 72% is coo0l
rechka_rhine: @yyube_ what's your operating system?
ivanfremn: Dsplits exactly
rechka_rhine: he's probably doing it to give us a better view
yyube_: @rechka_rhine I have access to a MacBook Pro 2012, a windows 10 professional PC I built, and a laptop I installed linux mint on.
ivanfremn: damn this man types faster than I think
Dsplits: Install ubuntu on a virtual machine
slaterusa: r u still being sued by every company under the sun?
thisisweeezy: Valuable
rechka_rhine: nice
rechka_rhine: windows is kinda shitty to learn programming on
thisisweeezy: nice
ido1m: @Dsplits why tho if he has mint installed already?
dorkmo: float on
gigafact: antergos is cool
Dsplits: Then use mint
yyube_: I don’t understand Linux at all tho
yyube_: Lol
arxenixOW: geohot did you do google ctf?
inoahdev: do you ever use an IDE?
rechka_rhine: lol
ivanfremn: someone duel this man on typeracer
yyube_: I just have it installed on a laptop
yyube_: Never actually have used it
slaterusa: what's he on that makes him type at 9 trillion mph
thisisweeezy: weeed
yyube_: I want to see Geo’s wpm on typeracer
ivanfremn: ^
rechka_rhine: me 3
Dsplits: @tomcr00s3 What is your wpm
thisisweeezy: godspeed
slaterusa: jfc
ivanfremn: Look at chat my man, we need you to prove your skills on typeracer
yyube_: True lol
thisisweeezy: next stream idea: typerace with twitties
yyube_: So about Linux. Where should I go for that?
slaterusa: @tomcr00s3 whatcha drinkin
rechka_rhine: install ubuntu if mint is confusing
ivanfremn: he codes inside of a freezer in order not to overheat
gigafact: https://antergos.com/
arxenixOW: @tomcr00s3 did you do google ctf?
inoahdev: do you twitch often?
rechka_rhine: then you just log in and open the terminal
rechka_rhine: and read the tutorial I sent you
rechka_rhine: or just use the macbook
gigafact: @inoahdev follow the stream to get notification when he starts streaming!
rechka_rhine: macos is easier and the terminal works exactly the same as on linux
metatlas: Coding Alpha Zero?
metatlas: Or something simpler?
slaterusa: real 1337 folks just write their own BIOS in assembly at boot-up and take it from there. Anything less, and you might as well be a secretary at Walmart HQ
yyube_: K, I really want to learn Linux
rechka_rhine: windows has a completely different terminal
gigafact: @slaterusa haha
yyube_: Windows seems like it sucks ass at everything programming related
rechka_rhine: if you learn the macos terminal, it's pretty much identical
yyube_: And Linux is really open source
ivanfremn: slaterusa LUL
Dsplits: For linux is mostly Unix commands that you need to learn
ivanfremn: dir > ls
yyube_: Mac is Unix based rights/
yyube_: Right?
Dsplits: yeah
rechka_rhine: yes
rechka_rhine: they descend from the same operating system from like the 70's
slaterusa: all hail the BSDs
ivanfremn: but linux is not unix
Dsplits: Mac OS is not a linux distro but is built on top of unix
slaterusa: shhh
Dsplits: linux is also built on top of unix
slaterusa: let's discuss Minix! that's fun!
rechka_rhine: plan9
rechka_rhine: urbit
slaterusa: hah, e
slaterusa: ew
ivanfremn: seriously this man is on some artificial enhancing substance
slaterusa: urbit is tainted by the involvement by that alt-right mongo
gigafact: https://wiki.archlinux.org/index.php/Arch-based_distributions
gigafact: anything arch based is great
slaterusa: @ivanfremn imma guess a bit of the ol' columbian marching powder
rechka_rhine: no, if you're getting started you install ubuntu
rechka_rhine: keep it simple, stupid.
Dsplits: @slaterusa Colombia
ivanfremn: go linux mint
slaterusa: @Dsplits oh yeh, my bad
yyube_: Should I use Linux on vm or install it on the computers? Or is it just preference?
slaterusa: @tomcr00s3 what's the keyboard ur using
rechka_rhine: shhh
gigafact: dualboot is fine
yyube_: That’s gotta be a Cherry MX blue
rechka_rhine: asking about keyboard is instaban
slaterusa: yeah
ivanfremn: it depends, if you dont need to use windows for anything I would go full Linux
ivanfremn: In fact I've tried many times, and failed
gigafact: ^ if you don't game you can go full linux
yyube_: I need windows because my brother shares PC and likes to play games
gigafact: dual boot then
Dsplits: use a vm
alluxua: I feel super interesting right now. Let us see how good geohot is!
yyube_: dual boot or VM?
ivanfremn: dual boot
rechka_rhine: dual booting would be hard for you to do
gigafact: ^wat no
joker2k999: lol
slaterusa: i always wonder if there's a market for a c64-form-factor pc-in-a-keyboard running a super-locked-down BSD walled-garden thing. Don't be stealing my ideas, brehz.
metatlas: Yeah, great idea.
metatlas: Do it!
slaterusa: thx
slaterusa: will do
metatlas: I'll buy.
yyube_: I know how to dual boot lol
metatlas: Just make sure I can make games with it.
yyube_: It’s whether I should or not
rechka_rhine: then why shouldn't you lol
ivanfremn: if you are gonna do everything on linux then dual boot
rechka_rhine: vms are slower
slaterusa: @metatlas nuh-uh. as i said, super-locked-down ;)
rechka_rhine: annoying to use
rechka_rhine: unless your computer's really fast
ivanfremn: there is no point in wasting resources on running two OS if you are just gonna use one
Dsplits: Just use a vm.. dual booting can fuck up your pc
ivanfremn: resources as in RAM and CPU
dorkmo: you did f2 to f4
ivanfremn: Dsplits how is dualboot gonna fuck up his PC?
metatlas: @slaterusa but the c64 could make games.
gigafact: @Dsplits dual boot does not fuck up your pc dumb people fuck up your pc
yyube_: I have an i7 4790k, gtx, 960, 8gb ram.
joker2k999: this is like gameboy chess
slaterusa: @metatlas talking form factor, not capabilities
yyube_: I don’t know if that’s fast or not
arxenixOW: is it playing against itself or against another AI?
yyube_: It gets the job done
metatlas: games for the same platform, not a full dev environment.
rechka_rhine: in visual basic
metatlas: so what are the capabilities?
rechka_rhine: to backtrack the IP
joker2k999: shoutout to black
slaterusa: @metatlas no viruses..? :D and also runs mail/web/openoffice / w/e
slaterusa: gheweee
metatlas: So kinda like an iPad?
gigafact: svg is great
slaterusa: @metatlas but with keyboard!
metatlas: I see. Yeah sounds good.
rechka_rhine: ipads have keyboards
slaterusa: @metatlas so, keyboard with an hdmi out, plug in screen, a winner iz u
metatlas: I think devices which don't connet to internet might be coming back.
slaterusa: (mouse via bluetooth)
ivanfremn: my toaster connects to the Internet
rechka_rhine: I don't think so
Dsplits: yes
joker2k999: no
Networks: I used to have a friend whose botnet was comprised mostly of microwaves
slaterusa: i keep losing connection.. lost chat
rechka_rhine: "a friend"
ivanfremn: I putted a bluetooth dongle on my dog
ivanfremn: now I summon him with a phone app
Networks: ill never admit to nuthin
rechka_rhine: good
rechka_rhine: you smaht
rechka_rhine: you loyal
gigafact: @slaterusa put your home router in bridge mode use some good router to keep connection up isp routers are trash
slaterusa: let's compromise ivan's dog-dongle
rechka_rhine: buy yo mom a house
slaterusa: @gigafact already have that setup. i think my housemates are abusing the bandwidth :/
joker2k999: i love this....George wakes up... I'm going to play chess today....no, wait, I'm going to write my own python chess AI program to beat me. #Winning
gigafact: lol if the setup is proper connection never dies
Networks: It's all fun and games until ivan's toasting is sending spam emails and mining shitcoins
ivanfremn: fml, just realized it is daytime again, should I sleep ?
Networks: toaster*
metatlas: compile the linux one for mac?
metatlas: if it works on linux, it should work on mac.
yyube_: Pfsense routers are lit
gigafact: Arch linux lol
slaterusa: @gigafact doesn't die, just slow. 7 housemates, welcome to San Francisco
tdools: @metatlas "should"
slaterusa: [insert linux distro name] linux, lol!
ivanfremn: Kanye West Linux
gigafact: use livestreamer and buffer the stream
rechka_rhine: @ivanfremn check out this website http://138.68.63.25:8000/
ivanfremn: that seems like a legit one
slaterusa: lol
idocrackforaliving: that site creeps me out
ivanfremn: clicks
slaterusa: everyone wants to be Mr. Black
rechka_rhine: @slaterusa his IP is 104.244.27.35
rechka_rhine: the rest is up to you
joker2k999: wuut? you don't know how to play chess
rechka_rhine: or maybe it's 88.200.98.58
rechka_rhine: hack them both just in case
rechka_rhine: hopefully the dongle is on there
Dsplits: lol
Dsplits: DDOS
rechka_rhine: that's not hacking
rechka_rhine: gotta start off with an nmap -p-
idocrackforaliving: its a ghost
joker2k999: the weeds kicking in
gigafact: too much lsd
Dsplits: oh shit.. home invasion
slaterusa: we all know the one true hacking is that kid who does a tracert and says "yeah this is hacking!!"
joker2k999: because the home invaders always answer back
slaterusa: @tomcr00s3 meeting with whomst?
idocrackforaliving: ur typing is satisfying
slaterusa: what on earth
ivanfremn: https://bit.ly/2ltR6vY
rechka_rhine: oh no
idocrackforaliving: i wouldnt click on it
rechka_rhine: gotta warm up the tor browser for this one
ivanfremn: Only the brave will take the risk
joker2k999: nope...
tdools: *opens dev tools on chrome* yea I'm a hacker Kappa
rechka_rhine: you can't backtrack me son
gigafact: http://www.wheredoesthislinkgo.com/
rechka_rhine: lol
slaterusa: only the brave will add a " " to a bit.ly link and see where it actually goes to...
rechka_rhine: ^
rechka_rhine: we have another hacker in our midst
gigafact: I am sure there is a hole in twitch so you can see all personal information of all people in here
ivanfremn: there has been 4 clicks on it
ivanfremn: yall ar part of my botnet now
rechka_rhine: I literally dox'd myself if you scroll up in the chat
rechka_rhine: but that's besides the point-
idocrackforaliving: i use a vpn
joker2k999: yesterday..
idocrackforaliving: #norisks
slaterusa: ..all my troubles seemed so far away...
rechka_rhine: all vpns are run by the NSA as far as I'm concerned
rechka_rhine: and really, you should call a proxy a proxy
slaterusa: don't use VPNs, then. Sorted.
ivanfremn: dat moment when the FBI asks PIA for your data and you already paid 10 years in advance
joker2k999: damn. that was quick
joker2k999: ..thats what she said
tdools: mdyGG
slaterusa: bad html, that's why
rechka_rhine: that moment when you make a honeypot and tell the FBI to drag you to court so you can tell everyone you don't have logs
joker2k999: next level server game bro
slaterusa: lol how do i html
idocrackforaliving: the image is scuffed
slaterusa: namespace SVG issue?
twitchinstl: Open developer tools and turn off any file cache in’s
joker2k999: autoreload?
slaterusa: lol broken image
idocrackforaliving: i think its the image
slaterusa: look at the source
slaterusa: huh.
idocrackforaliving: oh </img>
slaterusa: wtf img tags don't need to be closed
slaterusa: or at least don't need closing </img> dubya tee eff
idocrackforaliving: oh ya
idocrackforaliving: weird
slaterusa: or maybe some bizarro SGML-y thing
thisisweeezy: html is real programming
hartator1: should be onClick
thisisweeezy: damn, next level shit, import jquery
rechka_rhine: missing quote
rechka_rhine: onclick
michiamozen: "he's probably missing a semicolon"
rechka_rhine: wtf is big tag
thisisweeezy: <BIG>
Dsplits: import bootstrap
idocrackforaliving: thats what she said
thisisweeezy: this is great: python jquery html in .py
idocrackforaliving: stole ur joke
dorkmo: <BLINK>
hartator1: lol blink
thisisweeezy: omg
kabiroberai: The double quote in .post interferes with the onclick tag
dorkmo: <MARQUEE>
thisisweeezy: <template>
thisisweeezy: vanilla js
idocrackforaliving: blinks xd
thisisweeezy: high level front-end skillz
gigafact: hahaha it's so bad
dorkmo: party100
thisisweeezy: party1
thisisweeezy: yeeeeeah
yyube_: Those chess moves tho lol
thisisweeezy: moves yeaaaah
Networks: type="Submit"
thisisweeezy: submit yeeeaaaah
any_available_username: yeeeeeeaah
thisisweeezy: ooooh yyyeaaaahhhh~
thisisweeezy: <BIG> yyyyyeahhh
thisisweeezy: <BIG> font </BIG> yeeeaaaah
imaginepeanuts: what language are you programming in? this is super impressive! i'd love to properly learn how to code one day
thisisweeezy: goal1
gigafact: python and start soon
alluxua: shamrock1 shamrock1
thisisweeezy: YEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEAH~
3dvinci: Everything is gonna be alright
tdools: python is great to start with @imaginepeanuts
demonaso: i find python to be too hard for starters idk
gigafact: @demonaso false
alluxua: shamrock1 shamrock1
imaginepeanuts: i'm majoring in computer science starting this fall actually. i can check super quick what language the intro to cs class is
demonaso: prob c
thisisweeezy: smoke some weeed and write python!
thisisweeezy: pride1
alluxua: Python is super easy. You can crack it in 4 weeks if you code 6 hours a day
3dvinci: Intro probly Java
tdools: @demonaso c hurts mah brain
imaginepeanuts: They start us off in python
3dvinci: Interesting
imaginepeanuts: yeah i honestly thought it'd be java...but the university im going to is supposed to be super tough so
idocrackforaliving: harvard
imaginepeanuts: they're probably starting us off in python in order to weed out people sadly
gigafact: super tough LOL
dorkmo: i think its about time for a yerba mate
imaginepeanuts: not harvard @idocrackforaliving
thisisweeezy: YEEEEEEEEEEAH
imaginepeanuts: gt
thisisweeezy: party1
Crabtr: We're webdevs now! Kappa
gigafact: it only took 4 hours to get to this point
idocrackforaliving: if you do real crack you'll go to harvard
tdools: mdyLUL
alluxua: Harvard even doesnot offer deep learning for undergraduate
thisisweeezy: real webdev brooo
idocrackforaliving: sad
michiamozen: Nf3
idocrackforaliving: an ai that creates its self
michiamozen: maybe
michiamozen: try Nf3
thisisweeezy: ohhhhh nice
thisisweeezy: party2
michiamozen: me me
idocrackforaliving: nope
tdools: next step, how to chess mdyGG
thisisweeezy: grand master in the making!
michiamozen: he lost
michiamozen: rip
michiamozen: what
tdools: GivePLZ MrDestructoid TakeNRG
Autokriator: bishop to f7 and you wouldve won
alluxua: Geohot lost?
michiamozen: Bc4 to f7 and it could been game
michiamozen: Nf7
thisisweeezy: this is real twitch shit -- live streaming competitive sports: chess
michiamozen: the delay....
thisisweeezy: noooooobs
idocrackforaliving: 0-0
imaginepeanuts: so do any of you guys code as well ?
idocrackforaliving: ya
michiamozen: try o-o
imaginepeanuts: self taught?
idocrackforaliving: i did courses
tdools: same
thisisweeezy: 000000h!
imaginepeanuts: nice man
alluxua: I went to the top university with full scholarship, but learned nothing. Most of my knowledge and tech skills from long term self learning
thisisweeezy: nice commit message
gigafact: you learn yourself only way to be the best
idocrackforaliving: true
idocrackforaliving: im shit at coding
3dvinci: CS is the best field for learning yourself via internet
imaginepeanuts: i agree. even though i'm going into georgia tech this fall, i'm not naive enough to think that i'll become a great coder by just going to classes and doing homework
imaginepeanuts: it probably all comes from doing personal projects like this guy is doing rn
gigafact: George did a lot of other projects as well
gigafact: a lot
dorkmo: do you need ajax to stop the refresh?
3dvinci: Yea its all about what you've made
tdools: with any profession, it requires experience. and to get experience you have to go out on your own for the extra mile
alluxua: Georgia tech is very good at academic research, but not on application
idocrackforaliving: it would be amazing to go to m.i.t
imaginepeanuts: ahhh mit rejected me :((( its fine its fine
dorkmo: https://stackoverflow.com/questions/4285042/asynchronously-load-images-with-jquery
alluxua: Mit undergraduates CS classes are all on openware website
idocrackforaliving: ah ha moment
imaginepeanuts: I hear Harvard has a really good intro cs class online
3dvinci: CS50
alluxua: Harvard intro is on edx
3dvinci: That was the first thing I ever did wrt coding - years ago
thisisweeezy: party1
hartator1: yeah money
thisisweeezy: cheer1 oh yeeeeeeah $
idocrackforaliving: ho doesnt LUL
hartator1: why not using 2.7?
gigafact: you got a lot of donations on this stream
3dvinci: weeezy has a good strategy
gigafact: quite a few subs and bits
thisisweeezy: $ cheer1 $
vicious503: cheer1
alluxua: If you do love money, let us code LSTM on tesla stock price predictions next twitch
dorkmo: goal150
3dvinci: I'd watch
thisisweeezy: goal1
imaginepeanuts: tesla stock is literally a rollercoaster
thisisweeezy: goal1 50
thisisweeezy: lol
3dvinci: Elon based
thisisweeezy: twitch is a scam
gigafact: George you need to setup https://streamlabs.com/ they allow custom donations. A lot of streamers use it and you can set donation goals and so on
thisisweeezy: goal1 0000
alluxua: Geohot is in deep love with Tesla
tdools: @imaginepeanuts back test it on enron Kappa
dorkmo: goal1 0000000
thisisweeezy: Goal 11 0000000000000000000
thisisweeezy: goal1 000000000000000000
3dvinci: lol
thisisweeezy: goal1 000000000000000000000000000000000000000000
thisisweeezy: failed
alluxua: @thisisweeezy , you are damn adorable
idocrackforaliving: !cheer 5
idocrackforaliving: oof
idocrackforaliving: cheer5
thisisweeezy: thank you, yeeeeah, adorable
thisisweeezy: i can be geo's twitch language interpreter
gigafact: what was the peak viewers on twitchslam?
imaginepeanuts: does he have a twitter?
thisisweeezy: this probably has more
gigafact: @comma_ai twitter
thisisweeezy: twitter.com/commaai
thisisweeezy: commaai.com/rapgod
gigafact: ^bad urls
dorkmo: the only way to win is to not play
thisisweeezy: or go to pee for hours
alluxua: Twitch geohot is the best, periscope version is quite business, Twitter is fully marketing
thisisweeezy: oh yeeeeeeaaah
thisisweeezy: grand master
Autokriator: Is the training based on human games?
thisisweeezy: live from twitch
gigafact: improve quality how?
thisisweeezy: game collected from toddlers
alluxua: I think the training data is from human players
thisisweeezy: good job
thisisweeezy: documentations broooos, the most important part of the project
thisisweeezy: party1
idocrackforaliving: this is gonna be on github?
thisisweeezy: party1 000
gigafact: it's already
idocrackforaliving: oh
imaginepeanuts: this is some intense typing
thisisweeezy: github.com/geohot/twitchess or something
thisisweeezy: it's the keyboard
gigafact: https://github.com/geohot/twitchchess
idocrackforaliving: ty
imaginepeanuts: that's why i have a love hate relationship with mechanical keyboards. they're satisfying but also so loud sometimes
dorkmo: its gotta be the shoes
thisisweeezy: it is the shoes
thisisweeezy: ye shoes
thisisweeezy: party1 00
thisisweeezy: yall have a good night -- just in case geo peace out quick
thisisweeezy: party1 0000
dorkmo: twitch chess coin ico
thisisweeezy: raise b$llion$
alluxua: Your model is way too simple, the layers, Learning rate, kernel size never tuned
thisisweeezy: needs no tuning
alluxua: His model learned nothing
dorkmo: mspaint
thisisweeezy: learning yo party1 000
dorkmo: learning yeaaaaaaaaaaa
alluxua: I missed the loss function piece. What loss function he used?
thisisweeezy: hah
idocrackforaliving: xd
thisisweeezy: documentations yeeeeah party1 000
thisisweeezy: oh yeaaaah oh yeaaah MIT
thisisweeezy: yeahhh MIT yeaaaah oh yeaaah
dorkmo: party100 000000
thisisweeezy: party1 00 00
kabiroberai: What do you think about the current state of the iOS jailbreaking community? (If you’ve been keeping in touch with it)
thisisweeezy: it only take FOREVER to train
alluxua: Can anybody help to explain why he is using conv2d for training? I normally use reinforcement learning for this type of stuff
gigafact: you need CEO Nvidia V edition :D
thisisweeezy: oh yeeeah party1 0000
Networks: are you going to stream tomorrow?
idocrackforaliving: couldnt you create 1000s of simulations
gigafact: https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/2018/06/20/nvidia-ceo-springs-special-titan-v-gpus-on-elite-ai-researchers-cvpr/
thisisweeezy: hopefully by tomorrow, it can actually beat toddlers on chess
idocrackforaliving: nvidia is a scam
idocrackforaliving: LUL
thisisweeezy: GPPPPPUGE
thisisweeezy: beat these caaats
alluxua: Bro, I buy a lot of nvidia stocks. It is pretty good
thisisweeezy: haha
idocrackforaliving: dog is chill
thisisweeezy: so fuuuuny
thisisweeezy: defense brrrro
thisisweeezy: click click click party1 00
any_available_username: write it
thisisweeezy: tomorrow morning?
upsidedownlemon: yeah write it
upsidedownlemon: won't take too long
gigafact: write won't take too long...
alluxua: Yeah, write it! It is fun!
gigafact: maybe a few hours LOL
thisisweeezy: a PM, "it's not gonna take that long"
aziid1: stoopid
thisisweeezy: "aint it?"
thisisweeezy: javascript ninja
gigafact: what time is it there?
idocrackforaliving: its 1:46am for me
thisisweeezy: for me too
alluxua: He is in SF
aziid1: why not just shove everything in an RNN and call it a day, aye
thisisweeezy: ayyye
idocrackforaliving: 10:46pm 4 him
dorkmo: my laptop battery is going to die in 20 minutes
gigafact: connect to wall?
thisisweeezy: buy TSLA battery
idocrackforaliving: LUL
gigafact: TESLA for unlimited laptop life
thisisweeezy: gigfactor for your macbook
idocrackforaliving: *kills the pc instantly*
thisisweeezy: gigfactory
gigafact: 100KWh battery for laptop rofl
aziid1: clickety clackity clickety clackity clack clack
dorkmo: brb brushing teeth
aziid1: clickety clackity o no clickity clack
thisisweeezy: ooooh noooo
any_available_username: lmaoo
aziid1: click click clack clack clack
aziid1: im narrating for the hard of hearing
thisisweeezy: party1 00000
idocrackforaliving: the matrix
thisisweeezy: does anyone here has real job tomorrow lol
thisisweeezy: party1 000 0000
aziid1: u gotta do contracting, can charge more and work when you want
idocrackforaliving: PogChamp
alluxua: I do, but I work remotely
gigafact: better job than donating 1 bit at the time all stream lol
aziid1: might work tomorrow, might not
idocrackforaliving: work online
thisisweeezy: hah
thisisweeezy: so nice, work when I WANT to
gigafact: be your own boss
andrew_vy: you need to set an id on the element
aziid1: be your own bitch more like
gigafact: win in life
thisisweeezy: $buy $TSLA and chill on a beach
alluxua: I write ML to predict stock / crypto prices as side project, so kind of pretty free
idocrackforaliving: buy spacex and chill in space
thisisweeezy: nice
aziid1: if it worked it wouldn't be a side project
gigafact: @alluxua any good?
thisisweeezy: it could the next stream: ML predicting TSLA
thisisweeezy: lol
idocrackforaliving: can i buy america PogChamp ?
thisisweeezy: it loses ton of money party1 00 lol
aziid1: geohot do you always talk to yourself when working
alluxua: So far, 6 months, the worth monthly return over 60%. So pretty happy
aziid1: @tomcr00s3
thisisweeezy: 60% seriously?
3dvinci: Nice
idocrackforaliving: who doesnt take to them self
idocrackforaliving: talk*
thisisweeezy: BUY TSLA
thisisweeezy: yeeeeeeeeeah
alluxua: Well, if you hedge bitcoin, etherum with Costco, Netflix , google etc
gigafact: TSLA was up now it's a bit down
gigafact: BUY AMD
thisisweeezy: buy comma ai
gigafact: Thank you for the stream!
thisisweeezy: yeeeeeeeeah thank you party1 0000
any_available_username: byeeee
gigafact: This was fun
3dvinci: gn
aziid1: its only 11 pm bro
thisisweeezy: later party1 ,000, 000, 000
gigafact: almost 5 hours streaming
gigafact: good
thisisweeezy: thanks broooos
dorkmo: heyguys48 0000000
alluxua: Thank you, geohot. You are always wonderful even I feel you should polish your deep learning skills. No matter what, thank you! You motivated me a lot!
thisisweeezy: order another curry from thai
gigafact: it will be uploaded on youtube soon
aziid1: can you stream work on comma ai
thisisweeezy: it's great already go sleeeeep yeeeeeah
any_available_username: so lets sync our sleep schedule, how many hours you gonna sleep ? Kappa
nic0latesla: thank you geohot
thisisweeezy: lol
thisisweeezy: that's 3 more move than I do
thisisweeezy: smashes the subscribe button
any_available_username: :(
thisisweeezy: geo thinks 3 more steps of whore
Networks: This makes me miss the shkreli coding streams
aziid1: shkreli coded?
Networks: Yeah, he was doing NodeJS stuff
aziid1: i liked his stock analysis vids, learned a lot
Networks: with sockets and stuff
aziid1: y tho
thisisweeezy: nice profile picture
idocrackforaliving: geohot
alluxua: I love geohot profile picture
thisisweeezy: shoot for the star land on the moooon
thisisweeezy: party1 000,000,000
Networks: toodles
idocrackforaliving: cya
thisisweeezy: seee yall
renatorabelo: This guy is funny !
thisisweeezy: good night
gigafact: stream dead?
Networks: george sleep